Welcome to the new feature introduction video of Marvelous Designer 2025.
In the current version, you can turn on the side and back UVs of the expanded version.
Let's open the default T-shirt first to see the updated content.
In the 3D window, first change the clothing rendering type to the dense texture surface.
When you turn on the dense texture surface, you can see the material picture and the thickness of the side at the same time.
Select all panels and adjust the rendering thickness in the property editor.
When the thickness is increased and the rendering is improved, you will get a more obvious effect.
If you need to check the UV layout, please go to the main menu window and open the UV editor.
Select all panels.
In the property editor, select the side option under the expanded UV.
At this time, the side UV of the panel will show the thickness of the panel.
The side UV of the panel with the rectangular outer frame is extremely expanded.
Then select the panels in the back and open the back UV expansion of these panels.
Then move the front and side UV of the back panel to the side.
You will see the generated panel back UV.
The black outer frame is the front and side UV.
The independent one is the panel back UV.
If the back UV expansion is closed, you can't see it and you can't edit the back UV.
Now we put the front UV in one line and the back UV in one line.
Then export the object file.
When exporting, you need to keep the UV layout.
Please click on the unified UV coordinate N.
Click on the option you need to select and then click OK.
Then import the file into Substance Painter to view the UV image.
You will see that the UV image has been correctly arranged and exported.
You can see the additional material on the back side and side panel.
Now we re-add the material for the outfit.
You can see the UV on the side and back panels are correctlyских and there are no problems with the wrong rendering.
Now we can add the new corresponding UV.
Thank you.